(this.webpackJsonpexquiz=this.webpackJsonpexquiz||[]).push([[0],{14:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')},39:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(52)},44:function(e,t,a){},45:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a.p+"static/media/logo.5d5d9eef.svg"},51:function(e,t,a){},52:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),r=a.n(n),o=a(16),i=a.n(o),c=(a(44),a(45),a(31)),l=a(9),s=a(14),m=a(90),u=a(96),d=(a(46),a(95)),h=a(97),y=a(92),f=a(98),p=a(94),g=a(82),w=a(84),E=a(99),v=a(86),b=a(88),_=a(89),C=a(85),S=a(87),A=a(91),W=Object(g.a)((function(e){return{paper:{padding:"6px 16px"},secondaryTail:{backgroundColor:e.palette.secondary.main}}}));function q(e){var t=W();return r.a.createElement(w.a,{align:"alternate"},r.a.createElement(E.a,null,r.a.createElement(C.a,null),r.a.createElement(v.a,null,r.a.createElement(S.a,null),r.a.createElement(b.a,null)),r.a.createElement(_.a,null,r.a.createElement(m.a,{elevation:3,className:t.paper},r.a.createElement(A.a,{variant:"h6",component:"h1"},e.score,"%"),r.a.createElement(A.a,null,"Your Score")))),r.a.createElement(E.a,null,r.a.createElement(C.a,null),r.a.createElement(v.a,null,r.a.createElement(S.a,{color:"primary"}),r.a.createElement(b.a,null)),r.a.createElement(_.a,null,r.a.createElement(m.a,{elevation:3,className:t.paper},r.a.createElement(A.a,{variant:"h6",component:"h1"},e.correct),r.a.createElement(A.a,null,"Correct Answers")))),r.a.createElement(E.a,null,r.a.createElement(v.a,null,r.a.createElement(S.a,{color:"primary",variant:"outlined"}),r.a.createElement(b.a,{className:t.secondaryTail})),r.a.createElement(_.a,{variant:"secondary"},r.a.createElement(m.a,{elevation:3,className:t.paper},r.a.createElement(A.a,{variant:"h6",component:"h1"},e.wrong),r.a.createElement(A.a,null,"Wrong Answers")))),r.a.createElement(E.a,null,r.a.createElement(v.a,null,r.a.createElement(S.a,{color:"secondary"})),r.a.createElement(_.a,null,r.a.createElement(m.a,{elevation:3,className:t.paper},r.a.createElement(A.a,{variant:"h6",component:"h1"},e.totalQuestions),r.a.createElement(A.a,null,"Total Questions")))))}var F=a(93),O=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)([]),t=Object(l.a)(e,2),a=t[0],o=t[1],i=Object(n.useState)(null),g=Object(l.a)(i,2),w=g[0],E=g[1],v=Object(n.useState)(0),b=Object(l.a)(v,2),_=b[0],C=b[1],S=Object(n.useState)(!1),A=Object(l.a)(S,2),W=A[0],O=A[1],M=Object(n.useState)(!1),j=Object(l.a)(M,2),N=j[0],k=j[1],H=Object(n.useState)(!1),B=Object(l.a)(H,2),T=B[0],I=B[1],x=Object(n.useState)(0),D=Object(l.a)(x,2),G=D[0],R=D[1],K=Object(n.useState)(0),J=Object(l.a)(K,2),z=J[0],U=J[1],L=Object(n.useState)(0),P=Object(l.a)(L,2),V=P[0],Q=P[1];return Object(n.useEffect)((function(){if(o(s),!T){for(var e=[decodeURIComponent(s[_].correct_answer)],t=0;t<s[_].incorrect_answers.length;t++)e.push(decodeURIComponent(s[_].incorrect_answers[t]));var a=function(e){for(var t,a,n=e.length;n>0;)a=Math.floor(Math.random()*n),t=e[--n],e[n]=e[a],e[a]=t;return e}(e),n=Object(c.a)({},s[_]);n.options=a,"hard"===s[_].difficulty?n.rating=3:"medium"===s[_].difficulty?n.rating=2:n.rating=1,E(n)}}),[_]),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},T?r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(m.a,{elevation:3,className:"quizArea"},r.a.createElement(p.a,{severity:"info"},"It's Result Time"),r.a.createElement(q,{score:Math.round(G/V*100),totalQuestions:a.length,correct:G,wrong:z}),r.a.createElement(y.a,{variant:"contained",fullWidth:!0,color:"secondary",className:"startAgainBtn",onClick:function(){window.location.reload()}},"Start Again"))):r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(u.a,{striped:!0,variant:"warning",now:w&&(_+1)/a.length*100}),w&&r.a.createElement(m.a,{elevation:3,className:"quizArea"},r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Question ",null!==_&&_+1," of ",a.length),r.a.createElement("h6",null,"Category : ",decodeURIComponent(w.category)),r.a.createElement(d.a,{name:"read-only",size:"small",value:w.rating,readOnly:!0})),r.a.createElement(F.a,{style:{marginBottom:"20px"}}),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("p",null,decodeURIComponent(w.question))),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"optionsContainer"},w&&w.options.map((function(e,t){return r.a.createElement(h.a,{label:e,onClick:function(){var t;t=e,W||(Q(V+1),O(!0),t===decodeURIComponent(w.correct_answer)?(k(!0),R(G+1)):(k(!1),U(z+1)))},variant:"outlined"})}))),W&&r.a.createElement("div",{className:"alert"},r.a.createElement(p.a,{severity:N?"success":"error"},N?"Correct Answer, Well Done":"Sorry, Wrong Answer")),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(y.a,{variant:"contained",color:"secondary",fullWidth:!0,disabled:!W,endIcon:r.a.createElement(f.a,null),onClick:function(){_+1>=a.length?I(!0):(O(!1),k(null),C(_+1))}},"Next")))),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"scoreBarTxts"},r.a.createElement("p",null,"Score : ",isNaN(Math.round(G/V*100))?0:Math.round(G/V*100),"%"),r.a.createElement("p",null,"Max Score : ",Math.round((G+(a.length-V))/a.length*100))),r.a.createElement(u.a,null,r.a.createElement(u.a,{striped:!0,variant:"warning",now:Math.round(G/a.length*100),key:1}),r.a.createElement(u.a,{variant:"success",now:Math.round(G/V*100),key:2}),r.a.createElement(u.a,{striped:!0,variant:"danger",now:Math.round((G+(a.length-V))/a.length*100),key:3})))))};a(51);var M=function(){return r.a.createElement(r.a.Fragment,null,r.a.createElement(O,null))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(M,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}},[[39,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2908c59a.chunk.js.map